But this...
Initiating docking procedures.
Roger.
Elevating from 6 to 9
on the Torino Scale!
CITY A – HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
The course suddenly shifted?
I see.
Then we will discuss how best
to deal with the situation.
Should I go now?
All right.
Master, for some reason
the Hero Association
wants me to come in.
I will be back later.
Okay. Maybe you're getting fired?
THE ULTIMATE DISCIPLE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
CITY Z HERO ASSOCIATION BUILDING
Ah, you would be Genos?
My name is Bang. Nice to meet you.
Bang, Class S rank 3,
a.k.a. "Silver Fang."
He possesses true skill.
The Association called me in.
Everyone's at Headquarters.
This little branch office
is empty just now.
Each of the Class S heroes
got the call to come here,
but we're the only ones
who showed up.
Why is that?
Too far away, or perhaps they're busy.
Of course, some of the more
cold-blooded  ones simply don't bother.
After all, we're called up only
when there's some impossible problem
they want us to take care of.
Today's no exception.
The threat level is Dragon,
a worst-case scenario.
35 minutes from now,
a huge meteor will strike City Z.
They are asking if nearby Class S
heroes can do anything about it.
A meteor?
Apparently, it suddenly changed paths.
That means the end for us.
The impact will wipe out City Z.
I'm afraid there's nothing
we can do this time.
You too should think about
evacuating with your loved ones.
Do the citizens know?
I was told they would estimate
the impact area
and issue evacuation orders
30 minutes before it hits.
Attention! This is an announcement
from the Hero Association.
People are sure to panic.
And you, old fellow?
"Old fellow", is it?
Call me Bang.
You are not evacuating?
My dojo has been in my family
for generations.
I cannot abandon it.
"Fist of Flowing Water
Crushing Rock."
Heard of it?
He left...
Emergency evacuation warning.
The threat level is Dragon.
Evacuate immediately.
21 more minutes
until meteor impact.
It's huge...
No way we can escape that.
So many people have
given up hope of survival.
It is not just City Z
that is in danger.
The neighboring cities will
also sustain damage.
It is too late to evacuate.
I did not expect to be testing
this prototype so soon!
Let me see if an attack from
my incineration cannon at full power
will do the trick.
Master Saitama lives here too.
I cannot possibly
evacuate without him.
Is that...?
You are Bofoi, correct?
And you are the new boy, Genos.
Come to stop the meteor?
Yes.
Class S rank 7.
A hero who uses intense firepower
to obliterate his opponents along
with everything in their vicinity.
Does he also live in City Z?
Or did he rush here,
putting his life at risk?
Bofoi. I need your help.
I refuse.
Why?
I only came to field test
my new weapon.
The meteor is a perfect target.
A test?
If that meteor hits,
you too will die.
– I will not.
– What?
What you are talking to right now
is a remotely-controlled drone.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but my life's not at stake here.
Also, I am not Bofoi.
I am "Metal Knight."
Heroes call each other by
their hero names, not real names.
Everyone knows that.
Looks like it's time to
end our little chat.
All right!
Firing missiles!
Metal Knight?
I cannot fire with his missiles
in the way.
Amazing.
Such destructive power.
This hero is dangerous.
I must be wary.
Not quite potent enough, eh?
33 seconds left until impact.
To fire my incineration cannon
at full power,
I need five seconds to charge it
with my body's energy.
But the target is already close.
And if I do take it out, what then?
The meteor may break apart
and still cause a disaster.
But even before that,
will my weapons
be powerful enough to stop it?
Even Metal Knight's countless
missiles had no effect.
First off, be calm.
I see you've lost composure.
You are far too young
to be worried about failure.
When your back's up against
the wall, just muddle through.
The outcome won't change.
So that's what is best.
Muddling through is best...?
He is right.
If the outcome will not change...
then I how can I die
without giving it my all?
Bang, get down!
Oh.
I will no longer think about
failure or repercussions!
I will just pour everything I have...
...into one last shot!
Dammit, it is not working!
No! I think I see the meteor
being pushed back.
Really?
Oh, no. It was just my imagination.
You old fool!
So this...will be my grave.
Nine more seconds.
Get out of here, Bang.
Old man, take care of Genos.
Who...who are you?
I'm a hero.
Master?!
You're not...
gonna fall...
on my town!
He shattered it!
Unbelievable!
But...
It's collapsing...!
It's not just this building.
The destruction is spreading
through the whole city.
Guess that settles that.
THREE DAYS LATER
Although City Z was able to
avoid total destruction,
the city was still devastated,
with the effects of the meteor
fragments visible everywhere.
If only the Hero
Association had called...
you to help instead of me, Master.
If you had worked
with Metal Knight,
the damage
could have been minimized.
But that Metal Knight guy...
wasn't interested
in helping, right?
So stop worrying about it.
I think we kept the damage
to a minimum.
After all, no one died.
He is right.
Master's punch killed
the meteor's momentum.
Theoretically, the shockwaves
from the meteor
would have annihilated everything.
Stopping it was nothing
short of a miracle.
I would not be surprised
if people talk about Master
for years to come,
praising him as a man of courage.
But Master has no idea.
Some of the public is even
making him out to be the bad guy
for causing the partial
destruction of City Z.
No, I should not mention it.
By the way,
do you think we moved up in ranking?
Yes, we did.
I went from Class S rank 17 to 16.
Metal Knight also moved up
from rank 7 to 6.
Master, you shot up from
Class C rank 342 to 5.
Number 5?!
From 342 to 5?
What the hell?! That's crazy!
Not at all.
Your performance was worthy
of Class A or even Class S.
After all, it was threat level Dragon.
Yeah?
If there had been no damage,
I am sure you would be
at Class S rank 5.
Smashing the meteor alone
was worthy of Class A.
But I think the Hero Association
assumed that
Metal Knight and I played a big role.
By the way,
they always report threat levels
as "demon" or "tiger"
or whatever.
Does all that mean anything?
It does...
Tiger: A crisis threatening
massive loss of life.
Demon: A crisis threatening
to halt the functioning of an entire city,
or its destruction.
Dragon: A crisis threatening
the destruction of multiple cities.
God: A crisis threatening
human extinction.
GUIDE TO THREAT LEVELS
Wow...I had no idea.
I believe heroes often
consider threat levels
when deciding to respond or not.
But I guess
they do not matter to you.
Well, of course not.
If the heroes run away,
who's left to help?
What are you doing?
I must record your words.
Anyway, it wasn't all that much
for such a huge jump in rank...
All right.
I'll be out for a bit.
You are going out, Master?
I will come with you.
You stay here.
If something happens,
you'll get all the credit again.
This place has been wrecked...
Oh.
My favorite supermarket
got smashed.
And the crappy apartment building
I got kicked out of is...
Just fine...damn.
Hey.
You cheating bastard.
Uh...who are you?
You know damn well
I'm Tank-top Tiger!
Brother!
It's that guy!
Seriously, who is this guy?
You called me, little bro?
Brother!
The hero Tank-top
Black Hole...
is here!
So you're the fraud who
takes credit for work done
by Class S heroes in order
to jump the rankings?
What the—?
No one could move up
to number five so quickly
without cheating.
What do you guys want?
Huh? Isn't that obvious?
To beat you up so bad...
- you'll never be able to—
- Hang on, little bro.
Bastards like him don't learn
from that kind of lesson.
Let's make him really pay...
with the most brutal method there is.
Are you the one?!
The jerk-off responsible
for destroying this city?!
I get it!
There are tons of people in this city
who are angry with him.
Unbelievable!
How can you show your face?!
I see what he's doing.
He's going to use their anger...
Do you feel nothing at
the sight of this devastation?
...to break his spirit!
You're gloating,
thinking you've actually
saved these people!
Why else would you be walking around
so shamelessly?
Thanks to your screw up,
these citizens have nowhere to go!
If you were gonna fail this hard,
why'd you butt in?!
The other heroes would
have done a way better job!
And yet you still wanna play hero,
even after causing such
a huge disaster?
Look at this place!
All this destruction is your doing!
That's right.
I-It's your fault!
They took the bait.
You hear that?
The heart-wrenching cry
of someone who lost his home!
Look at them all, victims of
your thoughtless actions!
That's right!
Yeah, you tell him!
Haven't you even thought
to take responsibility?
Yeah!
You're inhuman!
Give up being a hero!
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up!
- Give it up!
- Go on, get outta here!
- Get lost!
- Give it up!
- Beat it!
- Scram!
- Give it up! Give it up!
- Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
We got him.
His pride should be
shattered by now.
That's what he gets for cheating...
That idiot!
m 0 0 l 1400 9 1400 84 0 84
CITY Z FORUM – IS IT TRUE
A CLASS C HERO DESTROYED THE TOWN?
- Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
- Give it up! Give it up! ive it up!
- Give it up! Give it up!
Is this what you call
mob mentality?
They're all chanting in unison.
Give it up! Give it up! Give it up!
Saitama...
Without a doubt,
you saved this city.
Yet look how the city treats you.
This is reality, though.
You're strong, the strongest man
I've ever seen.
That's why I refrain
from saying anything.
I'd hate to see you rotting away
in this industry.
Resigning is also an option.
Time to finish him off!
Hey!
He's getting ready to fight!
Huh? What are you talking—
No way!
You're gonna take out
your frustration
on these people here,
just like you destroyed their city?!
Do you just kill everyone
you don't like?
I won't let you do that!
We, the Tank-top Brothers,
will not stand by
and let you resort to violence!
If you're a hero,
then fight us fair and square!
So they're out to crush a rookie
and perform a publicity stunt
at the same time.
I'd say they've gotten a little greedy.
No wonder they can't rise
above Class B.
Yeah!
Go, Tank-top!
Do it!
Tank-top Tiger,
who fights like a true tiger, and...
Tank-top Black Hole,
who crushes all
with a grip strength of 2,800 psi!
We brothers will punish all
who stray from the path of the hero!
Huh?
Damn it!
I'll rip you apart!
I give up! I give up!
You're crushing my hand!
Huh?
You're kidding, right?
I give up for real.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for lying!
No, you weren't lying.
I'm the one who smashed
the meteor!
Anyone with a complaint,
let's hear it.
Speak up!
Because of you,
my brand new car was—
You can shut up!
Why would I give a crap
about your problems?
Tell it to the meteor, jackass!
Listen up!
I don't do this hero-thing
for admiration!
I do it because I want to!
So if you wanna blame me,
go ahead!
You baldies!
You're the baldy...
What'd you say?!
Master.
Oh, it's you, Genos.
Hang on.
These guys—
Let's go home,
Master.
Oh yeah?
Dammit. That guy's face
is burned into my brain.
I'm gonna remember this.
Master.
I have never met any person
as incredible as you, Master Saitama.
What brought that on?
You're creeping me out.
Even if the public
doesn't appreciate you,
I will still follow you.
You don't have to
butter me up. Really.
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
I heard there's some amazing hero
in Class C right now.
Class C?
The guy who says
he smashed the meteor, right?
That's just a rumor.
Going after weak guys,
then calling yourself a hero?
Just shows that there's no hero
you can really count on.
NEXT
EPISODE
THE DEEP SEA KING
My name is Bofoi.
You all may know me better as Metal Knight.
Next time on One-Punch Man Episode 8:
"The Deep Sea King."
Oh, the king of the sea, eh? Pretty cocky.
Wonder what he's like...